

PROJECTS

<u>Splitzy</u> — Receipt Storage + Mobile Payment App

Captures, digitizes and stores receipts, automatically splits costs, and attaches proof of purchase in payment requests. Designed to help users keep track of shared costs. Conducted user surveys, competitive research, crafted user personas, stories to define solutions; developed user flows, wireframes, branding, prototypes; ran usability tests. Built on Figma.

<u>MyCloud</u> — Cloud Storage + Content Creating App

Developed to help business professionals and students manage files, deliver projects, and collaborate with peers. Allows easy access on all devices, refined organizational features, and provides a safe place for storing files. Conducted user research, competitive analysis, usability tests. I designed the concepts, brand, and prototypes through Figma and InVision.

EXPERIENCE

PoolUp — *UX Researcher*Remote | September 2020 - Present

- Recruit targeted end-users, conduct stakeholder and client interviews
- Identify and evaluate key research opportunities; plan and implement user research strategies
- Collect and analyze user behavior through various surveys, studies, analyses; use data and customer feedback to make design decisions

Vert Energy Group — *Energy Compliance Manager* Irvine, CA | June 2018 - Present

- Responsible for coordinating the data collection, performing data entry, and report generation for ongoing energy reporting and benchmarking services, prepare annual client-facing deliverables
- Prospecting, managing sales leads, cold outreach, hosting webinars, customer support via a CRM software
- Writing and enhancing sales and marketing templates; developing and expanding into new markets nationwide
- Administrative support, assist project teams with compliance documentation and project tracking; staff training and management

EDUCATION

Bloc, UX Design Apprenticeship

Remote | November 2019 – September 2020

Learned industry best practices and design process standards with a focus on UX Research, Visual Design, and Front-end development. Created and deployed projects while learning new tools and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a senior product designer.

University of California, Bachelor of Arts in Environmental Studies Santa Barbara, CA | October 2014 – June 2018

PORTFOLIO

www.priscillavu.com

CONTACT

(714) 592-5009

priscilla.vu@aol.com

linkedin.com/in/priscilla-vu/

SKILLS

User Surveys

User Research Design

Affinity Mapping

Persona Building

Content Strategy

Brand Design + Identity

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Low to High Fidelity Prototyping

Usability Testing

TOOLS

Figma

InVision

Sketch

Photoshop

Git + GitHub

HTML5 CSS3

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)

Vietnamese (Native/Conversant)

Spanish (Basic)